Steen, Ivan; Papers apap219
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Oral History and Research Files, 1936-2013; Undated; 1; 3.72
  - Victor Lord, Interviews and Articles, [RESTRICTED], 1984; 1987; Undated (Box 4 (1-Oral History and Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Interview with Victor Lord, [RESTRICTED], 1984 March 08 (Cassette 166-167)
  - WGY Interview of Ivan Steen, 1984 December 27 (Cassette 169)
- University at Albany History Department, 1965-2013; Undated; 2; 1.2
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains material related to the University at Albany's History Department and the Graduate Public History programs. There are large amount of memorandum sent out by the department as well as material about undergraduate and graduate committees. There are also multiple files about HIS 497, which is the department's honors program seminar class. There is one folder pertaining to the University's Social Studies Department.
  Several files in this series document the establishment of the Master's in Public History Program directed by Ivan Steen. Materials include correspondence, program overviews, and newsletters. There also is a file related to the 19th Annual Conference of the National Council on Public History, which was held in Albany. Professor Steen served as chair of the Local Arrangements Committee and on the Program Committee.
  - Social Studies Department Bulletins, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 1)
  - History Department Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 2)
  - History Department Bulletins, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 3)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 4)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 5-6)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 7)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 8)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 9)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 10)
  - History Department Placement, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 11)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 12)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 13)
  - History Department, HIS 497, Fall, 1974 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 14)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 15)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 16)
  - History Department, HIS 497, Fall, 1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 17)
  - History Department, HIS 497, Spring, 1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 18)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 19)
  - History Department Undergraduate Course Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 20)
  - History Department Undergraduate Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 21)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 22)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 23)
  - Public History Program Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 24)
  - History Department Evaluation, 1982 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 25)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 26)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 27)
  - History Department Newsletters, 1983-1984; 1987 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 28)
  - Public History Program Overview, 1983; 1986; Undated (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 29)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 30)
  - Public History Program Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 31)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 32)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1987-2000 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 33)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 34)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 35)
  - Public History Program Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 36)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 37)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 38)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 1)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 2)
  - 19th Annual Conference of the National Council on Public History, 1997 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 3)
  - Public History Program 20th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 4)
  - Rock and Newbold Scholarships, 2002-2004 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 5)
  - Public History Program Newsletters, 2002-2006; 2008-2009 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 6)
  - The FBI in Action May 1, 1943 Staging at Researching New York Conference, 2004 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 7)
  - Public History Program 30th Anniversary, 2013; Undated (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 8)
  - Career Networking for History Students, Department of History, Undated (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 9)